

#### Contact

Phone (+94) 77 533 0847

Email asirinadun222@gmail.com

Address No.10, Thelawala Rd, Mount Lavinia, Colombo, Sri Lanka.

Social Media
@nadunsilv

### **Portfolio**

URL: https://nadunsilv.github.io/

## **Education**

2014 - 2016 Higher National Diploma in computing & Software Engineering ICBT Campus

2014 - 2015
PCJT Software Engineering
Java Institute for Advanced Technology

2012 - 2014 GCE Advance Level - Commerce Stream Isipathana College

# Language

English Speaking

English Writing

Sinhala • • • • •

# Asiri Nadun Silva

Software Engineer

### **Profile**

I am self-motivated, energetic, flexible, person willing to do continue learning. I have good team working and leadership skills which I have achieved through my academic work and extracurricular activities. My objective is to develop skills, apply innovative thinking and be an example to the society I live in.

I have almost 5 years of experience and created many websites & applications on different stacks.

# **Experience**

May 2020 - Present Software Engineer

APS Lanka (Pvt) Ltd

After a long lockdown period due to the covid-19 pandemic, I joined APS Lanka as a Software Engineer. One year later I became the head of the IT department. Here, as a team, we manage the company's social media accounts, email servers, and developed internal software requirements under my supervision.

Jul 2018 - Feb 2020 (1 yr 8 mos)

Sky digital (Pvt) Ltd

Associate Software Engineer

After successfully completing the internship, I got an opportunity to become the Assistant Software Engineer in this company. Here, I have successfully completed Few Ecommerce, Business, Classified websites & web bases softwares like Stock handling, Point of sales.

Dec 2017 - Jun 2018

Steadfast Technologies

Software Engineer Intern

(7 months)

I completed my internship, gaining the best experience of my career. With the help of senior developers, I was able to create several business websites and a web based invoicing system (Pure PHP).

## Skills

PHP Codeighiter Laravel Flutter C# .net SQL Server

API Handling / GIT

••••

Wordpress Shopify Magento

Node JS /Vue JS
IPG Intergration

IPG Intergration

Photoshop / Illustrator

Reference

MR. Priyanga Siriwardhana, Senior lecturer, ICBT campus, Colombo 05, Srilanka. Mobile: 071 810 0985 MR. Niroshana Sampath, Senior Project Manager, APS Lanka (Pvt) Ltd, Kaduwela, Kothalawala. Mobile: 071 810 0985 / +971 52 50 5302